badmintoncentral.com 2018-08-11

# Privacy Policy | Badminton Central

INFORMATION WE GATHER

The information we gather falls into two categories: 1) personal information you voluntarily supply when you complete a survey, register as a user on our FORUM, enter a contest or provide your e-mail address, and 2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our sites.

USE OF INFORMATION

If you have registered or signed up on BadmintonCentral, we will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address without your permission. This also applies to any information that personally identifies you, except as noted immediately below.We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website(s); or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

We do, however, share information about our audience in aggregate form. For example, we may want to know how long the average reader spends on our site, or which pages or features get the most attention. BadmintonCentral may perform statistical analyses of readers and their reading patterns for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on our Web sites to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent.

FORUM USE

Any information you disclose when posting to our FORUM, along with your message board screen name or ID, becomes public, and BadmintonCentral has no control over how readers may use or treat what you post or divulge.

EMAIL CORRESPONDENCE

If, at any time, you prefer not to receive email newsletters or correspondence from us, simply follow the unsubscribe options at the bottom of each e-mail.

AMENDMENTS TO THIS POLICY

Our Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this Privacy Policy page.
